baps.org 2019-09-29

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

The detailed terms and conditions related to this website, application, skill or software (‘Software’) are provided in the ‘Terms of Use and Service’.

In brief, we assure users that this Software does not use advertising and does not sell or exchange your personal information with any other entity.

The personal information which you have submitted to the website on any page or form will only be used for the purpose for which it was collected as identified on the page or form. It will not be used for any other purpose and it will not be disclosed without your consent. The personal information you provide will be held by us and made available only to staff authorised to deal with the error indicated, or service requested, or information provided on the form. If you provide your contact details, we may contact you to provide feedback, or for further information regarding the form you have submitted. The provision of the information is voluntary, however, if you do not provide the information requested we may not be able to provide you with service you are seeking. We will take reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Should you wish to access or amend this information please Contact Us at info@swaminarayan.org.

**Third Party Advertising**

The Website does NOT use any Advertising and does not give, sell or exchange any information gathered from the Website visitors. However, the Website may link to external websites which may use advertising. We encourage visitors to check the Terms and Policies of any website that is linked from this Website.

**Email Policy**

We do not collect, sell, rent, or otherwise distribute email addresses or any other personal information. All discussions by email or on any other medium are seen only by authorised personnel who keep the communication confidential unless we obtain consent from you or the email itself contains a request to be forwarded to other persons.

**Please Note**

Our Privacy Policy is subject to change. This policy was last updated 14th Jun 2019.

**Cookies Policy**

**www.BAPS.org** ("us", "we", or "our") uses cookies on our websites (the "Website"). By using the Website, you consent to the use of cookies.

This website does not sell any personal information regarding or gathered from the visitors of our Website.

Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third parties that we may partner with may use cookies on the Website, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.

**What are cookies**

An HTTP cookie (also called web cookie, Internet cookie, browser cookie, or simply cookie) is a small piece of data sent to your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your computer by your web browser and allows the Website or a third party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Website more useful to you. The cookie will collect information relating to your use of our sites, information about your device such as the device’s IP address and browser type, demographic data and, if you arrived at our site via a link from third party site, the URL of the linking page etc. If you are a registered user or subscriber it may also collect your name and email address, which may be transferred to data processors for registered user or subscriber verification purposes.

**How the Website uses cookies**

When you use and access the Website, we may place a number of cookies files in your computer by your web browser. We use cookies for the following purposes: to enable certain functions of the Website, to provide analytics, to store your preferences, to enable information delivery. These cookies DO NOT identify, you, nor do they store personal information, but just the action of your use of our website. We also have a cookie, that remembers your acceptance of our cookie policy.

We use both session and persistent cookies on the Service and we use different types of cookies to run the Service. We may use essential cookies to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts.

LIST OF SOME COOKIES AND THEIR FUNCTIONS :

**Cookie**

| 

**Type**

| 

**Usage**  
  
---|---|---  
  
ASP.NET_SessionId

| 

Session

| 

used for login  
  
DisplayName

| 

setting

| 

used for login  
  
vview

| 

Session

| 

used for setting view preference  
  
www.baps.orgportalroles1

| 

Session

| 

used for login  
  
cookies_consent

| 

setting

| 

used for cookies consent  
  
whatsnew

| 

setting

| 

used for user view setting  
  
Third party cookies

| 

Google Analytics

| 

used for data analysis  
  
Third party cookies

| 

Cloudflair.com

| 

used to apply security settings  
  
Third party cookies

| 

Facebook.com

| 

Used to share contents on social media, e.g. Facebook.com  
  
We employ customised statistic analytics which uses session cookies that expire after each session which we use to identify what country you visit from, what methods and how you come to visit our site, including whether you came direct to our site or from another website and the URL of that website.We also try to identify if you have visited us from a search engine such as Google or Bing and for what search string you used, or whether it was from a bookmark. We also follow and note the pages you visit. We may collect or store the Internet protocol address (IP) from which you visit. For security reasons, we may at times turn on our log analyser, to ascertain, where a attempted security breach is taking place and that will log IP's.

**What are your choices regarding cookies**

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser. Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.
